Different-colored eyes
Hair the color of fire
A couple of personalities within me
Be more careful
Atone for your sins
We are sacred flames
We're not as bad
As you think
Come a step toward me
Raise your white flag
I'll bite until there's blood
Don't ask for mercy
Dissolving into silence
Your voice in the depths
Will tell a secret to the river
I seem different to you
If you want, receive love
But don't forget that this gift isn't mine
You should not have looked into my eyes
And don't drown afterward in your tears
A white dress in the wind
A curse upon you
I need embraces, kisses, happiness
The ashes of pain scattered
I run through the field
With you into the heavens
You and I are like magic
Too bad, nothing awaits at the end
I don't know what we should do
It will be easier to let go
It seemed to me you loved
But you were deceiving me
The book of life will burn
You'll find no more pages
You should not have looked into my eyes
And don't drown afterward in your tears
A white dress in the wind
A curse upon you
I need embraces, kisses, happiness
The ashes of pain scattered
I run through the field
With you into the heavens
A white dress in the wind
A curse upon you
I need embraces, kisses, happiness
The ashes of pain scattered
I run through the field
With you into the heavens
A white dress in the wind
A curse upon you
I need embraces, kisses, happiness
The ashes of pain scattered
I run through the field
With you into the heavens